<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>terraform on melastmohican.github.io</title>
    <link>https://melastmohican.github.io/tags/terraform/</link>
    <description>Recent content in terraform on melastmohican.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 12:36:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://melastmohican.github.io/tags/terraform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Best Practice Guide for Developers</title>
      <link>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/terraform_best_practice_guide_for_developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 12:36:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/terraform_best_practice_guide_for_developers/</guid>
      <description>Terraform is an open-source infrastructure as code software tool created by HashiCorp. It enables users to define and provision infrastructure using a high-level configuration language known as Hashicorp Configuration Language (HCL), or optionally JSON. Terraform is platform-agnostic; you can use it to manage bare metal servers or cloud servers like AWS, Google Cloud Platform, OpenStack, and Azure. Terraform enables you to safely and predictably create, change, and improve infrastructure. It is an open-source tool that codifies APIs into declarative configuration files that can be shared amongst team members, treated as code, edited, reviewed, and versioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating existing AWS infrastructure to new acount</title>
      <link>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/aws-resource-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 13:37:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/aws-resource-migration/</guid>
      <description>Scenario We want to migrate hundreds of AWS resources to a new account. Up to now, all resources were created manually using AWS Console or CLI tool.
CloudFormation CloudFormation is the inhouse cloud provisioning tool of AWS for declaratively describing your cloud resources.
CloudFormation is a hard, complex, inconsistent and badly documented piece of software. A stack is an atomic collection of resources in CloudFormation. Its creation or update succeeds only and only if all the resources within the stack succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>