<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>melastmohican.github.io</title>
    <link>https://melastmohican.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on melastmohican.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 14:24:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://melastmohican.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maven Archetypes Project Templating</title>
      <link>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/maven-archetypes-project-templating/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 09:50:53 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/maven-archetypes-project-templating/</guid>
      <description>Intro I am developer and I like DRY. If there is any task you have to do more than once you should probably automate it. starting a new project, it can be tedious and time-consuming to start over and over again from scratch. You can use Spring Initializr to boostrap your new application or even better without leaving the shell Spring Boot CLI. You will get nice clean project with the latest versions of dependencies but what if you need to use specific internal libraries or configuration files?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://melastmohican.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 14:24:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melastmohican.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>It should be noted that no ethically-trained software engineer would ever consent to write a NukeChicago procedure. Basic professional ethics would instead require him to write a NukeCity procedure, to which Chicago could be given as a parameter.
Why did the API go to sleep? It needed some REST.
There are 10 types of people in this world, those who understand binary and those who don&amp;rsquo;t.
How many programmers does it take to change a light bulb?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating existing AWS infrastructure to new acount</title>
      <link>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/aws-resource-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 13:37:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melastmohican.github.io/posts/aws-resource-migration/</guid>
      <description>Scenario We want to migrate hundreds of AWS resources to a new account. Up to now, all resources were created manually using AWS Console or CLI tool.
CloudFormation CloudFormation is the inhouse cloud provisioning tool of AWS for declaratively describing your cloud resources.
CloudFormation is a hard, complex, inconsistent and badly documented piece of software. A stack is an atomic collection of resources in CloudFormation. Its creation or update succeeds only and only if all the resources within the stack succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>